Previously on From...
Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
No. no. no. no. no. no!
Don't touch me!
Don't. don't. No! Don't!
Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
Don't touch me!
Hey! Hey! You okay?
Did you see them?
See what? See who?
We heard a voice on the radio.
He knew my name. Knew what my
wife was doin' in the house.
In the basement. Jim...
I think people are watching us.
We've gotta start
working together on this.
I gotta go. Jim.
You were on your way to
rehab and you ended up here.
Did you take anything from here?
It was just a little
bit of morphine so I...
Marielle.
Yeah. fine. Do whatever
the fuck you want!
They're coming.
You have to get out
before the music stops.
My blood...
"is your blood now."
Look. I got worms under my skin.
and it feels like something's
coming for me now.
We can't have new people
stealing what
little food we have!
Get outside!
Dale. come on.
Get off me! No!
Help!
Boyd! Kenny! I'm gonna
need you up here!
I can't breathe!
Breathe in again.
Kristi. what's happening?
I'm gonna relieve the
pressure. all right?
You can't put my blood
into him. Boyd...
Whatever's inside me is
going to go into him!
Boyd! Boyd!
I got an idea.
My blood is your blood
now. motherfucker.
I almost lost him!
But you didn't. okay?
I need to ask you something.
Yeah. of course.
Do you have any pregnancy tests?
Are you sure?
As sure as I can be.
given the circumstances.
Have you said
anything to Ellis yet?
Uh. no. no. not...
not yet. I. uh...
I know these aren't the
most ideal conditions.
but women have been giving
birth for thousands of years.
Right.
And...
not all of them have
a third-year medical student
to guide them through.
Look. talk to Ellis.
the three of us can...
I can't. I...
I don't want to say
anything to him yet.
Hey. sun's coming up.
Yeah. We'll be right there.
Fatima. what's going on?
Fatima... We should go.
Sorry. We should go.
All right.
You good?
Jesus.
You really did it.
You killed one of them.
What do we do with the body?
We should burn it.
No.
We take it inside.
Tell me you're joking.
No. he's right. This is...
This is our chance
to learn about them.
We could study
them. open them up.
see what they look
like on the inside.
We... we don't even know if
it's safe to touch this thing!
You're talking about...
about operating on it!
You guys...
Kristi.
It's your call.
Let's bring it in.
I'll get a sheet.
We can drag it.
Thanks.
I'll grab some sticks.
Ellis. I need you to head
back up to Colony House.
No. I wanna stay.
Look. you do that. we're
gonna have dozens of people
comin' to check on you. and
we gotta keep this quiet.
At least until we have a
chance to get a look at it.
Hey. uh. Kristi. are you
good if we head back?
I mean. yeah. but you
gotta take it easy.
You come back to me immediately
if you have any trouble
breathing. okay?
Keep the bandage nice and dry.
and I'll check on you later.
Okay. 'Kay?
Let's go. Yeah.
Elgin.
Yeah?
What?
You all right?
I'm fine.
Be careful.
Yeah. Always.
Let's go.
You guys.
All right. can we pl...
can we please just stop
and talk about
this for a second?
Kenny. what is
there to talk about?
You're about to willingly bring
something evil into your home!
Do you understand that?
I do. I also understand
that we may never get
this opportunity again.
So is that it?
Okay?
All right. Let's go.
Is Ellis gonna be okay?
How the fuck should I know?
I spent the whole night
putting food in salt water.
Hmm. What are you
gonna do with me?
You gonna put me in the box?
That's what they'd do down
there in the town. right?
Is that who we are now?
I'm sorry about what happened
to Ellis. I really am. He's a...
He's a good kid.
But I'm not wrong about
those people from the bus!
There's too many people here!
I saw how much food you
brought down yesterday.
There's some hard
choices coming.
and no one here seems
willing to make them.
I'd be careful how much
you lobby for people
to make hard choices.
No one gets in or out.
Right.
So what happens now? We
see how Ellis is doing.
And then what?
You can't honestly
expect us to live here
with someone who
tried to kill us.
He wanted us to go outside
in the middle of the night!
He was ready to put both
of us out into that...
Yeah. I heard the recap.
And I'm asking you what
you're gonna do about it.
- Look...
- Donna!
The van just pulled up.
Ellis and Fatima are back.
Listen.
I promise you.
you are safe here.
and we are gonna
figure this out.
You're one of us.
That fuckwad in the
room notwithstanding.
we take care of our people.
Okay! Everyone!
Come on! Give him room! Okay!
Oh. fuck.
Okay. Okay. Lean right on me.
Okay. We got ya. Here we go.
Okay. here we
go. Easy does it.
Easy does it.
I think we should flip them.
No.
But they're ready.
They're not ready.
Hey. never argue
with a master chef.
You're giving away the
secrets of the trade. huh?
I wanna see Victor today.
Oh. well. I don't think
that's a good idea. buddy.
Why not?
I could take him.
I was gonna go up there anyway.
Nobody's going to Colony House.
Hey. Jim. I think it's
okay for them to go.
Okay. Uh. can we talk
outside for a minute?
Save me some pancakes. okay?
What's up?
I don't know what's
going on with you...
Excuse me?
We have to be a team here.
So when I say no one
goes to Colony House
and you immediately undermine
me. it doesn't help.
Okay. what... what
do you wanna do?
Do you wanna lock
them in the basement?
Two days ago you took Ethan
to confront the person
that tried to kill him.
That was different.
No. it was you and
I accepting the fact
that we can't just lock them
away until we find a way home.
You want them sneaking out?
Because that's what will happen.
This way we know
where they're going.
we know they're together.
I just don't want
our 9-year-old son
hanging out with some
emotionally stunted freak
who walks around town with
a gun in his lunch box.
Wait. wait. wait. No.
That emotionally stunted freak
saved your daughter's life
and he saved mine.
Or maybe that's what
they want you to think.
I heard a voice on the radio.
Why is that nothing for you?
Because I think you're wrong.
I know you want all
this to make sense.
I know you want there to
be a rational explanation.
but if you had been
down in those tunnels.
if you'd seen what I saw...
Or maybe that's what
they wanted you to see.
Oh. God.
Okay.
Hmm.
How did they do it?
How did "they" create monsters
that come out at night?
Because I've seen those
things up close. Jim.
I've seen them.
You're so sure this voice
you heard on the radio
is the answer to all
those impossible things.
Have you ever stopped to wonder
if that voice was even a person?
Of course it's a person.
What else do you think it was?
I don't know.
And that is fucking terrifying.
You know what? But for now.
I'm gonna go back inside
and have pancakes
with my children.
You're welcome to
join us if you want.
Okay.
You got it?
All right.
Okay. so how's this work?
What do you need?
It looks like it has
some sort of rib cage.
so we'll probably need a saw.
Okay. uh. there's a few of those
in the tool shed by the bar.
Ugh. Gloves wouldn't
be a bad idea either.
All right. Hey. Kenny.
you think your mom has
anything in storage
that we can use?
Kenny?
You had worms or something
crawling underneath your skin.
and you put them inside this
thing and now it's dead.
Yeah?
So what happened to the worms?
Huh? Are they dead. too?
- What do you...
- Excuse me.
Mari! Hey!
Hey. Mari.
Oh. honey. Hey.
Come on. baby. Come here. Hey.
I'm sorry. It's okay.
Is she okay?
She's going through withdrawal.
Uh. is there anything we can...
I need gloves and something
to cut through bone.
I don't want this
thing down here
any longer than it needs to be.
so let's just do it
and get it done. okay?
Please.
Hey. come on. let's go.
Let's get you cleaned up. okay?
I'll. uh... I'll go
down to the shed.
Hey.
Sorry about the flyby. I
was just fucking around.
That's all right.
You're pretty good
with that thing.
It's supposed to be for
my nephew's birthday.
Figured I'd get
my money's worth.
Hey. I...
I never thanked you for
what you did the other day.
helping out down
in the basement.
Well. you're welcome.
Though. seeing as your
wife wasn't even down there
it kinda seems like you got
those two other guys
killed for nothing.
That feel good just
now saying that?
Buddy. fuck off. okay?
You said thank you.
You're welcome.
What else do you want from me?
How much do you think
that thing can carry?
What? Why?
Take a walk with me. I
wanna show you something.
Where?
Just down the
road. outside town.
Oh. you want me to help
find your dog. right?
What?
You sound like one of
those fucking perverts
that hang out at playgrounds.
What is wrong with you?
It's... Just leave
me alone. okay?
What if I told you that
drone might get you home
in time for your
nephew's birthday?
Did they move again?
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
Go away.
Why are you being so mean to me?
I thought we were friends.
We are friends.
Doesn't feel like it.
I'm trying to protect you.
It's just...
It's safer for you
to stay away from me.
Why?
'Cause bad things happen
to my friends here.
Well. what's the point of being
friends if we can't be friends?
Okay.
Bye.
The orange was dry.
What?
The markers you gave me.
The orange was dry.
It was a bad gift.
Sorry.
There's a lot of
measuring to do.
I guess you can help
if you... if you want.
They need you out there.
They can wait.
Just go.
There.
I'll be fine.
You're shivering. Here.
Just do what you need to do.
Just try and drink
some water. okay?
Yeah.
I'll be right back. Mmm-hmm.
She okay?
Not great. She's
trying to sleep.
Okay.
Let me help you with that.
I'm...
She's gonna be all right.
you know? She's got you.
Uh. when I met her she'd
been sober for almost a year.
She worked so hard.
she was so proud.
And then I disappeared.
Hey.
Hey. listen.
This is not on you.
I didn't even notice she
was going through withdrawal
because I was so caught
up in that fuckin' thing!
I... No. Kenny's right.
We have no idea what we're in
for once we open that thing up.
I know.
Are you scared?
Yeah.
Yeah. Me. too.
Okay.
Yeah!
You know it's a bar. right?
You don't have to knock.
What are you doing?
Well. you've arrived
at a fortuitous time.
I think I figured out
how to make the alcohol
not taste like stomach acid.
I needed a project
that wasn't terrifying.
Hey. come on. could you
give me a hand with this?
No. I actually need
to ask you a question.
Um...
When you found me in
the woods the other day
I was rolling on the
ground and screaming.
you were not surprised.
Why?
I like you a lot better when
you're not yelling at me.
Oh. come on. Jade. Just...
Just answer this
question. please.
Your husband found me
like that once before.
He ever tell you that?
No. no.
Well. to be fair. I wasn't
entirely forthcoming
with the details.
If I recall
correctly. I got up...
and I told him to fuck
off. and then I ran away.
What happened?
I was being attacked by a
very angry Civil War soldier.
What?
That's all you get.
You want more. you
gotta help me with this.
And you're not
allowed to yell at me.
You sent out a call for help.
someone actually answered.
and no one's doing
anything about that?
Yeah.
And you think this is one
big mindfuck designed to...
designed to what?
See what we all do?
Experiments have been going on
like this for a long. long time.
And when you see the ones
that finally get declassified.
you start to wonder
about the ones
they still manage
to keep under wraps.
Holy shit.
That's where you and your...
Yeah.
Fuck.
Come on.
The key is the antenna.
We're gonna have to get the
signal up over the treetops.
That's why we put it on
the roof the last time.
Yeah. if we can strip
this thing down.
get it light enough. this
drone could carry it up over...
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I get it.
You can get the antenna up as
high as you want. All right.
This radio's pretty trashed.
Oh. the radio's not the problem.
I can handle the radio.
Sure about that?
Huh. You think I'm crazy.
I don't think you're crazy.
Shit. with everything
I've seen here so far.
you're the first person
that's making any sense.
I'm just wondering why
you haven't asked yourself
the obvious question.
And what's that?
Well. you think this place
is one big experiment. right?
And it never occurred to you
that some of the people here
might be in on it?
I mean. they'd have to be.
How else do you keep
the experiment on track?
Jesus. He stabbed you?
Yeah. things have been a little
intense around here lately.
But you guys are both okay?
We're fine. Yeah.
Really. we're fine.
Okay.
Okay. Well. I'll let
you get some rest then.
Hey. Come here.
Mmm.
I miss you guys.
We miss you. too.
You're always welcome here.
You know that. right?
Yeah. I do.
And you guys are always
welcome at the Liu house.
We'll keep that in mind.
Oh! Jeez! Sorry!
Whoa!
Leaving so soon?
Uh. yeah. I gotta
make sure my brother's
not building a spaceship
or something with Victor.
Well. best get on that then.
Bye.
I thought you two
might be hungry.
And I thought we were in the
middle of a food shortage.
We are in the beginning stages
of a minor and
temporary shortage.
But you need to get
your strength up.
Donna. I am fine.
Really. I am.
But it never should have
happened in the first place.
I should've been here.
I'm sorry.
Well. I am so glad
that you have finally
decided to apologise.
because another grown man
losing his shit and stabbing
me is clearly your fault.
You know what I mean. smartass.
You did good.
Getting him down to the clinic.
Hey. Julie?
Oh. hey. Hey.
You know. we have to
stop meeting like this.
On the... on the porch.
Oh.
Yeah. right. Uh...
What's up?
You said if I ever
wanted to talk...
Yeah. Yeah. yeah. Of course.
Uh...
We have time for a walk?
Okay.
These are all I
could find. so...
Yeah.
Yeah. they're fine.
All right.
How can I help?
Catch me if I fall?
Sorry. bad joke.
I'm gonna open up the shirt.
Okay.
I'll take. uh...
I'm. uh. just gonna make an
incision across the chest. okay?
Here we go.
Fuck!
It-it-it's... it's fine.
I-I-I just... I think I just
hit a nerve or something.
No. no. no. no. no. no.
stop. Let's stop. stop.
It's fine... No.
wait. wait. just wait!
Kenny! Jesus Christ!
Stop! All right?
We shouldn't be doing this!
We should have
fucking burned it!
We shouldn't be doing this!
You are fucking crazy!
Hey! Jesus Christ!
Hey. hey!
I got it. I got it.
Kenny?
Kenny!
Kenny. stop.
Fucking stop!
Are you really gonna
walk away right now?
We never should have
brought that thing inside.
It's dead. How is
it going to hurt us?
I'm not worried about
the monster. Kristi!
I'm worried about the thing
that fucking killed it.
Kristi. Boyd brought
something back with him.
He had worms crawling
underneath his skin!
He put them inside
the scariest thing
I've ever seen in my
entire goddamn life.
and now that scary
thing is dead.
But that's why we need to...
Look. whatever Boyd brought back
is like a poison
to those things.
and now it's in his blood!
If we could extract
it and use it.
we may finally have a
way of fighting back!
Or there is something in
there that'll kill you
the moment you
open that thing up.
How do you not see that?
Fine. I'm willing
to take that risk.
Look. Kenny. all I do here is
put broken things back together.
This is a chance
to just finally...
And. yeah. I'm scared.
I'm fucking terrified.
and that's why I need
you in there with me!
I can't do this without...
We're in this
together. remember?
You and me.
No.
No. we're not.
Not anymore.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No. I'm... That's
all... I'm saying...
Look. look. it's okay.
It's okay.
I'm glad she's here.
Truly. I am. I...
Kristi. I love you.
And all I want is for
you to be happy. but...
but I can't go in there
and watch you do something
that might get you killed.
I just... I can't do that!
I just can't.
I'm sorry.
Kristi!
Kristi?
No.
No. no. no. no. no!
Kristi! Kristi!
You feeling okay?
Where is it?
What?
The body. the fucking body...
Run.
I ca...
Marielle. run!
Hey. Donna.
Hey.
Are you all right?
Plants keep dying.
It's like they're
growing in poisoned soil.
Boyd. all he ever
wanted was to find...
I'm pregnant.
Oh. sweetie!
Oh. this is...
Oh. I wish I coulda seen
Ellis's face when he found out
he was gonna be a dad.
I haven't said
anything to him yet.
Is he not...
No. of course he is. Um...
Donna. I was told
I can't have kids.
What's happening right now
is medically impossible.
And all I can think
is what if this place
is trying to torture me?
Mock me?
Like those things that
come out at night!
The way they smile at us.
What if this is just another...
What's happening?
I'm standing here thinking
I am at the end of the line.
that everything I thought
about this place was...
We have seen so much
unbelievable shit
in this place.
Roads that lead nowhere.
Monsters that come
from the dark.
According to Boyd.
there are evil fucking trees
that trap you in dungeons!
Don't ask.
The point is...
we have seen a lot of horrible.
impossible shit here.
So we just assume that
anything impossible
that happens here is bad.
But look at you!
Sweetie. you met the
love of your life
in the middle of your
worst fucking nightmare.
You're gonna have a baby
that you were told
you could never have!
That sounds like a pretty
good impossible to me!
Donna. it's
impossible... Oh. what?
You're gonna sit here and
tell me with all you've seen
that you can't wrap your
head around a miracle?
Because a miracle is just the
other side of a nightmare.
What if you're wrong?
I've got a different
question for you.
What if I'm right?
There we go.
So first it was the guy crushed
by the rock in the root cellar.
He was stuffed inside that
giant armoire in the back.
And then...
And then it was the
Civil War soldiers.
and then the other
night. Christopher.
which was easily the
creepiest fucking thing
I've ever experienced
in my life.
Wait. Christopher?
Oh. yeah.
Christopher's the guy
holding the journal.
And you see that kid
in the background?
Yeah. that's Victor.
Wow. you caught that a
lot quicker than I did.
Okay. so...
For you. what you see
is different every time?
Yeah. I mean. except
for the symbol.
Why? What do you see?
I just see children.
What. like...
like. little kids?
Yeah.
Yeah. but...
they're fucking terrifying.
I thought I was losing my
mind or I was being punished.
Punished for what?
Well. my...
My son Thomas was a few
months old when he died. so...
You know.
Fuck.
God. I'm so sorry.
Well. look. I mean.
the good news is
you're not being punished.
Maybe this is just
a fucked-up place
where scary shit happens.
and there's no explanation why.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go home.
I appreciate the help.
Wait. is this the symbol
you were talking about?
Yeah. that's. uh.
Christopher's incel
book of crazy.
I've seen this.
Yeah? Like in a
vision or something?
No.
No. on the walls in the tunnels.
What the fuck?
What tunnels?
How many times we
have to do this?
A lot.
'Cause we have to be thorough.
We have to be sure.
They're losing their leaves.
What?
The trees.
So?
That happens every year.
Oh. not here.
It's always the same here.
Oh.
Mm.
Is it bad that they're
losing their leaves?
When things change
here. it's usually bad.
Well. if it's never
happened before.
maybe it's good.
Oh.
Almost got it.
There. There you go.
Okay.
Now we have to
remove the sternum.
Right.
What?
Okay. on the count of three.
Okay.
Hold that head steady. okay?
Uh-huh. One. two. three.
What the fuck?
What's wrong? What is it?
It's human.
I mean. at least it-it-it was.
It's got the exact same anatomy.
There are the lungs.
The heart. Liver.
But they're... shriveled.
Desiccated.
It's like some shit that
you see at a museum.
Hey. hey. look. slow down.
Just talk... just
talk to me. Just...
It's supposed to
be in the blood.
"My blood is your blood."
that's what you
said to it. right?
Right. I... Right.
But maybe their blood
is different than ours.
Yeah. right. This thing
is bone dry inside.
There's... There's... There's
no fluid. there's no lymph.
there's... there's
nothing... Hey. it's okay...
No. it's not okay!
This was our chance.
This. this couldn't have
been for nothing. okay?
There's gotta be
something in here.
Gotta be something in here.
There's gotta be something.
Shit. There's gotta
be something in here.
There's gotta be
something in here.
Come on. come on.
Aw. hey. be careful.
Piece of shit.
You fucking. fucking
piece of shit.
Okay. Fucking! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuckin' piece of shit!
Okay. Stop! Stop!
Kristi. hey. hey! Stop!
What is that?
What's that stuff?
That's the gallbladder.
That's. um...
That's bile.
It's bile. That's... it's
good. right? It's liquid.
That might be something
we can use. right?
Yeah. maybe. it's something.
Maybe? You're goddamn
right that's something.
Bile is something.
Bile is some... Hey. yo.
Could you get me one of...
Yeah. the droppers
so that we can...
we can collect it.
Look. yo. you did good.
You did great.
Wait. what do you
mean he killed it?
I'm telling you. he went
outside and did something
and the thing started screaming.
When we went out this
morning. it was dead.
Jesus.
You can't tell anyone.
Not even your parents.
Why?
I don't know. Boyd said he
doesn't want anyone to know yet.
and I really don't want him
pissed at me. so please...
Okay. okay. okay. I won't
say anything. I promise.
Look. this is a good thing.
I mean. if we can hurt them?
If we can kill them?
Everybody here is gonna
be a whole lot safer.
I know.
So why are you upset?
You know that dream I had?
On the bus?
Yeah.
I can't shake this feeling
like there's something
I'm supposed to remember.
Something that...
When I seen that thing lying
there in the dirt this morning.
it was like I could...
it was right there.
And I...
It was like before I could
move my head. it was gone.
And I...
I don't know if what I'm
supposed to remember is real
or if my mind is just
so messed up that...
No. no.
Everything about this is crazy.
I get it.
This pl... this
place. it's like.
as soon as you start to think.
"You know. maybe today
I won't go insane."
something new comes
along and it's like.
"Hey. wait till you see this."
We all go through it.
You seem pretty together.
Seriously?
You must be in pretty
bad shape then.
I do have this
little trick though.
for when things really
start to get to me.
What's that?
I fill up the bathtub.
and I sink down just enough
so that the water is
level with my ears.
And the sound is like
when you're standing
by the ocean.
And I just sit like that
for a while and I breathe.
It's peaceful.
I don't take baths.
Okay. well then. I don't
know how to help you.
Hi.
Hey.
I have just accepted that I'm
never gonna be comfortable again.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I am.
There's something
I need to tell you.
Big day.
Yeah. it was.
You really think injecting
them with that stuff's
gonna kill them?
Honestly. I got no fucking idea.
But it's the best chance we got.
How are we even gonna test it?
I tell you what.
Let's make that a
problem for tomorrow.
I should get home.
Uh. tell Kristi. you know...
Yeah. okay.
Hey. Kenny.
Hey. you ever want
that badge back...
I'll see you around.
Yeah.
How'd it go?
I don't really know yet.
I guess we'll have
to wait and see.
How are you?
I had a bad dream.
Oh. no.
What was it about?
That thing in the basement
came alive. and...
I think there was a music box?
Your friend Boyd's
giving me his nightmares.
I'll be sure to talk
to him about that.
I'm gonna be alright. you know.
You don't have to
worry about me.
- OpenSubtitles.com -
Synchronised by
Sunflower_king